const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    prompt: "But first, let’s say hello to each other!",
    type: "text" // Button where you can input text
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    prompt: "Hello {name}, where can we send you your custom remedy?",
    type: "text" // Button where you can input text
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    prompt: "Where can we reach you? <br /> <span class=alt>PS- Don’t worry. We won’t be spamming!</span>",
    type: "text", 
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    prompt: "Which of the following best describes you?",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Female", "Male", "Other" ]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    prompt: "How old are you? <br /> <span class='alt'>(Sorry but we have to ask) </span>",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Under 25", "25-35", "36-45", "Over 45"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    prompt: "How would you describe your wake up face? <br/> <span class='prompt-alternative'>Alternatively, what does your face feel like 15 minutes post wash?</span>",
    type: "mcq",
    answers: ["Tight & Dry", "Oily", "Oily in some places & dry in some", "Balanced & Normal"]
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    prompt: "Do you tend to have adverse reactions to <br/> certain skin care products or ingredients? <br/>  <span class='alt' >We're all made different so certain ingredients can cause irritation. We'll stay away <br/> from these for you </span>",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Yes", "No"]
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    prompt: " <span class='alt1'>What do you feel you need help with <br/> most? </span>",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["DrySkin", "Pigmentation", "OilySkin", "SensitiveSkin","Acne","CombinationSkin","TexturedSkin"]
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    prompt: "What is the pollution generally like where <br/> you live? <br/> <span class='alt'> PS - You're more than halfway through the questionnaire. Hold tight! </span>",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Chill", "Not chill","Out of control"]
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    prompt: "How much screen time do you get in a <br/> day? <br/> <span class='alt'> (Whoops! We’re all guilty parties here.) </span>",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Less than 2 hours", "2 hours or more"]
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    prompt: "Stress is no fun. How often do you find <br/> your self getting worked up?",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["A lot", "Sometimes","Not so much"]
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    prompt: " <span class='alt1'>How often do you struggle with dark <br/> circles or puffy eyes? </span>",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Less than 2 hours", "2 hours or more"]
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    prompt: "Ok this is a biggie. How many hours of <br/> sleep do you manage at night?",
    type: "mcq", // Multiple choice
    answers: ["Less than 6 hours", "6 to 8 hours","More than 8 hours"]
  }
];

export default questions;
